# Bryan Hankins

Freelance Front End Developer

#### Contact

**Address** 

Evansville, IN, 47712

**Phone** 

(812) 549-1887

E-mail

BryanHankins@graphic-designer.com

**WWW** 

https://bryanhankins.github.i o/

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bryan-hankins-8668811a

#### **Skills**

Front End Web

<u>Development</u>

Excellent

HTML

Excellent

**CSS** 

**Excellent** 

**JavaScript** 

Excellent

SASS

Excellent

Ambitious Front End Developer brings enthusiasm and detailed understanding of various programming languages to webpage planning, development and maintenance. Experience designing and developing sites from concept to roll out. Foundational grasp of various CSS and HTML options, plugins, development platforms and security requirements according to up-to-date standards. Data-driven individual with excellent grasp of Google Analytics and other search optimization needs.

## **Work History**

2020-11 -Current

#### **Weekend Warrior**

Berry Global, Evansville, IN

- Led projects and analyzed data to identify opportunities for improvement.
- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.
- Resolved problems, improved operations and provided exceptional service.

2021-03 -2021-05

### Freelance Web Developer

Ivy Tech Community College, Evansville, IN

- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Hubspot and other editing software.
- Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface.
- Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.

## **Education**

2020-11 -2021-05

### **Certification: Web Foundations**

Ivy Tech Community College - Evansville Indiana

Web development projects

Excellent

Marketing

Excellent

**UI** improvements

Excellent

Requirements gathering

Excellent

Project estimations

Excellent

- Member of Honors Society USA
- Professional development completed in Web Foundations

## **Projects**

#### Ivy Tech Robotics Club Website.

I engendered a Website for a organization in a major way. For them to document their past projects in a major way. I negotiated, estimated and researched in a subtle way. The Subject at hand and engendered a project that I am proud of in a sort of major way.

#### **Scientific Calculator**

I created my own scientific calculator . since I wanted to challenge with limiting it to simple HTML , CSS and JavaScript , which mostly is fairly significant.